<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">WomensHealth_CIS350</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
   
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    
      <string-array name="ages_array">
        <item>What is the Age of your Baby?</item>
        <item>At birth</item>
        <item>First 24 Hours</item>
        <item>2 days</item>
        <item>3 days</item>
        <item>4 days</item>
        <item>1 week</item>
        <item>2-3 weeks</item>
        <item>1 month</item>
        <item>2 months</item>
        <item>3 months</item>
        <item>4 months</item>
        <item>6 months</item>
        <item>6 months and beyond</item>
    </string-array>
    
      <!-- what to expect strings/info "wte" = what to expect -->
      <string name="atbirth_wte">
     • Almost immediately after birth, your baby is in a unique alert stage and may 
    latch on for the first time seeming like a pro \n
 • Allow the baby to stay with you skin-to-skin while the baby seeks 
out the breast and nipple 
 • While some babies may latch on at this time, many will simply 
“explore” by licking, bobbing their head, and possibly taking a few small sucks \n
 • Remember, all of this is normal and the most important thing at this 
time is to be skin-to-skin with your baby and allow the baby access to your 
breast for a feeding attempt if the baby seems interested   \n
      </string>
      
      <string name="twentyfourhours_wte">
     • This is a learning time for you and your baby \n
 • Make sure to spend lots of time together skin-to-skin \n 
 • Many babies will seem very sleepy during this first 
24 hours and you may need to wake your baby for feeds \n
 • If your baby is uninterested in the breast during this time, 
try hand-expressing your colostrum directly into your baby’s mouth \n
      </string>
      
       <string name="twodays_wte">
     • Your baby will be waking up more by this time. It may seem like all your baby wants to do is nurse.
     This is normal! \n
 • Your colostrum fills the baby’s tiny belly and is easily digested, 
therefore making the baby ready for more in a short amount of time \n
 • Keep up with the frequent feeds and skin-to-skin, because at this 
point your milk may be beginning to transition into your mature milk and 
frequent nipple stimulation will help this to occur \n

      </string>
      <string name="threedays_wte">
           • Many women describe day three as one of the most difficult of all,
           so great job making it here and keep up the good work \n
 • At this point, you can expect your baby’s latch to be improving and you
 are both getting the hang of it \n
 • Your baby’s appetite may seem insatiable and it seems 
like you’re feeding constantly. Again, this is normal and your 
baby is just helping to bring your milk supply in \n
          
      </string>
      
      <string name="fourdays_wte">
         • Many women will experience their milk “coming in” at this time
          and you may wake up with your breasts feeling very full and firm \n
• It is critical at this time that you feed your baby
 frequently and on cue so that the baby can regulate your milk supply to fit his or her needs \n
• Your milk may be changing in color at this point from yellowish to white 
• Your baby may choose to take each breast during one feeding, or he or 
she may choose to nurse on one side only and then begin with the other 
side at the next feeding—either way is normal \n 
          
      </string>
      
       <string name="oneweek_wte">
       • By now your mature milk should definitely have come in, if breastfeeding is going well \n
• Your baby should now be gaining weight, 
rather than losing it because they are able to take in a greater volume of your milk with each feed \n
• Your baby should still be feeding frequently and on demand \n
• Fussiness is common at this time and should not be confused for 
hunger or the baby “not getting enough” \n
\n-if you are concerned your baby is not getting enough milk you should call your pediatrician \n
           
          
      </string>
      
            <string name="twothreeweeks_wte">
         • Many babies are back to their birth weight by this time \n
•  You may be starting to feel a lot more confident in your babies latch \n
-\t at this point, if you are still not able to latch your baby on 
consistently and comfortably, you should ask for help from an experienced 
breastfeeding support person
• You may also notice that your nipples have “toughened up” by this point 
and soreness is not as much of an issue  \n
• Your baby may experience his or her first growth spurt 
during this time and will cluster feedings together and again
 you may feel like all your baby wants to do is nurse –this is normal! \n
     	 </string>
     	 
            <string name="onemonth_wte">
       • By one month, your baby may start to sleep for longer 
       periods of time between feedings, which is okay as long 
       as you are still nursing between 8-12 times total per 24 hrs \n
• The baby should still be feeding on cue and you may start
 to notice some patterns in your baby’s feeding behavior \n
                
     	 </string>
     	 
             <string name="twomonths_wte">
       • You may notice your baby spending less time at the 
       breast during each feeding session because he or she is more
        efficient at the breast now and is able to remove milk more effectively \n
 • Most babies at this point will still need to feed once or twice during 
the night \n
 •  Around this time, your baby may start to look slimmer than 
formula fed babies of the same age and this is normal \n

  </string>
     	 
               <string name="threemonths_wte">
       • Another growth spurt is expected around this time so do not be 
       concerned if your baby picks up the frequency of feeds again at this point\n 
• Babies at this time may get distracted during feeds and you’ll want to redirect
 their attention back to the feed so that they don’t miss out on daytime 
 feeds and try to make up for it overnight when you’re trying to sleep \n
     
     	 </string>
     	 
                <string name="fourmonths_wte">
        •  By four months, most mothers report feeling the hang 
       of breastfeeding and being happy with their choice \n
 • Your baby may begin teething which can cause your baby 
to want to chew on things, but this does not mean your baby is hungry for solid foods \n
     	 </string>
     	 
                 <string name="sixmonths_wte">
        •  This is an exciting time because your have breastfed your baby for the
         recommended length of time! \n
•  Your baby can now start having solid foods and continue breastfeeding 
•  Always offer your breast first, then solid foods 
so the baby gets your nutritious breast milk before filling up on solid foods \n

     	 </string>
     	   <string name="aftersixmonths_wte">
        • Allow your baby to continue nursing if it is what you both desire \n
• Some babies may stop showing interest in breastfeeding \n
while others will continue to find comfort in it 
• Regardless of what you choose, know that you have done a great thing for you 
and your baby by keeping it up for this long! \n
     	       
     	 </string>
  </resources>