<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name = "title_rooming_in">Expect Rooming-in</string>
    
    <string name = "next_step">Next Step</string>
    
    <string name="content_rooming_in">
      <p> Rooming-in is when you and your baby remain together
        for 24 hrs a day after your baby is born [picture]\n</p>

<font color='#9ED8D5'><p><b><i>Why should I room in with my baby?</i></b>  \n
<br>• Mothers who room-in with their babies \n</br>
	<br>\to Make more milk \n</br>
	<br>\to Make more milk sooner \n</br>
	<br>\to Breastfeed longer\n</br>
<br>• Babies who room-in with their mothers \n</br>
	<br>\to Are more likely to exclusively breastfeed \n</br>
	<br>\to Cry less \n</br>
	<br>\to Soothe more easily \n</br>
	<br>\to Spend more time quietly sleeping \n</br>
	<br>\to Take in more breast milk \n</br>
	<br>\to Are less likely to develop jaundice \n</br>
	</p></font>

<p><b><i>Won’t I lose sleep if I have my baby with me 24 hours a day?\n</i></b>
<br>\t• Studies show that mothers and babies who room in get the same amount 
of sleep as those whose babies are cared for in the nursery  \n</br>
<br>\t• Some moms may even sleep more peacefully knowing their babies are with them \n</br></p>

<p><b><i>Doesn’t my baby have to go to the nursery for tests and procedures? \n</i></b>
<br>\t• Many tasks like vitals signs, baths and blood draws can be done right in
your room.  Just make sure to ask your nurse if this is possible. \n </br>
<br>\t• Some procedures, such as a circumcision, may require that your baby
leave your room, but be sure to ask for the baby to be returned to you as 
soon after the procedure as is safe. \n </br>
<br>\to Did you know that breastfeeding can sooth an infant who is in 
pain?! After a circumcision is a great time to breastfeed your 
baby. \n</br></p>

<p>\t• Ask your provider before you give birth if the place you plan to deliver
has a policy on rooming-in and how they can help you achieve 24 hours of
rooming-in with your baby \n</p>

<p><b><i>The Bottom Line \n</i></b>
<br>\t• Rooming-in is best for mothers and babies to develop a successful 
breastfeeding relationship and should be done as long as the medical 
conditions of the mother and baby allow for it \n</br></p>
</string>

    
    
    <string name = "title_skintoskin">
<p> • Your baby should be placed skin-to-skin with you as soon as possible after 
birth if both you and your baby are medically stable \n
	<br>\to Make sure to ask your healthcare provider about skin-to-skin 
		before you have your baby so everyone is aware of your wishes \n
		</br></p>
<p>• Skin-to-skin should also be done with each breastfeeding attempt 
throughout the first few days after birth\n</p>
<p><font color='#EA8976'><b><i>What are the benefits of skin-to-skin?</i></b></font>
<br>• Babies who are placed skin-to-skin on their mothers immediately after 
birth \n</br>
<br>\to Cry less \n</br>
<br>\to Stay warmer\n</br>
<br>\to Have more stable blood sugars \n</br>
<br>\to Breastfeed sooner after birth \n</br>
<br>\to Are more likely to leave the hospital exclusively breastfeeding \n</br>
<br>\to Breastfeed for longer durations overall \n</br>


<br>• Frequent skin-to-skin contact in the first few days after birth has been 
shown to \n</br>
<br>\to Improve overall breastfeeding outcomes \n</br>
<br>\to Prevent infant weight loss \n</br>
<br>\to Increase mother’s milk supply\n</br>
<br>\to Promote mother-infant bonding \n</br>
</p>
<p><font color='#EA8976'><b><i>The Bottom Line</i></b></font>
• Think of skin-to-skin as breastfeeding class for your baby—your baby 
is learning a new skill and skin-to-skin is providing them with an 
environment in which they can get to know your touch, smell your milk, 
and have easy access to your breasts for when they are ready</p>
    </string>
    
    <string name="skinToSkin">Skin to Skin</string>
 <string name="title_exclusivity">Exclusivity</string>
 
 <string name="content_exclusivity">
<p><br>  <font color='#EA8976'><b>  Breastfeeding exclusivity</b></font> means that your baby receives only your milk from the 
time he or she is born </br>
<br>Colostrum is the only food that healthy, full-term babies need in the first few days 
after birth \n</br>
<br>	\t• A 1 day old baby’s stomach is about the size of a small marble or 5-7mL \n</br>
<br>	\t• You can trust that your colostrum is just the right amount for your baby’s 
	first feedings\n</br>
</p>
<p><br>Studies show that infant’s who receive only their mother’s milk in the first few
days following birth are more successful with breastfeeding, breastfeed for longer 
durations, and are more likely to be exclusively breastfeeding at 6 months of age </br>
</p>
<p><br>Why shouldn’t I give my baby formula if he or she seems hungry and my milk isn’t 
in yet?\n</br>
<br>\t • Your baby’s tummy is fragile and is designed to be coated with your 
colostrum, which protects it from getting damaged. Formula can interfere 
with this natural process and allow your baby’s tummy to let bacteria in 
which can be harmful to your baby \n</br>
<br>\t • Babies who receive formula are less likely to breastfeed as frequently, 
which can decrease your milk supply as well as delay the time to when 
your milk “comes in”\n</br>
</p>
<br><font color='#EA8976'><b><i>The Bottom Line \n</i></b></font></br>
<br>\t	• Trust in the fact that your body was designed to do this for you and your
	baby. You are capable of providing all the nutrition that your baby needs.\n</br>
 </string>
 
 <string name= "title_feeding"> Feeding on Demand </string>
 
 <string name="content_feeding">
<p><br>  <font color='#EA8976'><b>Feeding on demand</b></font> means that your baby has unrestricted access to your 
breasts and you allow them to feed when they are hungry \n </br></p>
<p><br><font color='#EA8976'><b><i>Is there a way to know how many times my baby should eat throughout the day? \n</i></b></font></br>
	<br>\t• Although the exact patterns will vary greatly between babies, it is 
	recommended that all babies feed 8-12 times per 24hr day in the first 
	several weeks of life \n</br>
	<br>\t• While some babies may choose to cluster their feeds every hour for 
	several hours during the day, and then space out their feeds to every 3-
	4 hours over night, other babies may do the exact opposite! Either way is 
	normal! \n</br>
	<br>\t• The key is that your baby feed 8-12 times per day and not go longer than 
	4 hours without offering your baby the breast \n</br></p>

<p><br><font color='#EA8976'><b><i>Why is feeding on demand so important? \n</i></b></font></br>
	<br>\t• Feeding on demand will allow your baby to regulate his or her own food 
	intake based on their small, but growing belly\n</br>
	<br>\t• Babies who nurse frequently in the early days of breastfeeding are more 
	likely to bring in their mom’s milk supply sooner\n</br>
	<br>\t• Limiting feeds by trying to put your baby on a schedule can lead to a 
	reduced milk supply and further breastfeeding complications\n</br></p>
	
<p><br><font color='#EA8976'><b><i>The Bottom Line \n</i></b></font></br>
<br>\t • Watch the baby, not the clock! Get to know your baby’s feeding cues and
allow the baby to nurse when he or she seems ready. Babies cannot tell 
time, so trying to put them on a schedule will only stress you and your 
baby out. Its important not that a baby go 2-3 hours between feedings, 
but that they get the correct number of feedings overall.</br></p>

 </string>
 
 <string name="title_pacifier"> No/avoid pacifiers/artificial teets
 </string>
 
 <string name="content_pacifier">
<p><br> When trying to establish breastfeeding, it is best to avoid giving your baby a
pacifier \n</br></p>

<p><br><font color='#EA8976'><b><i>Why should I avoid giving my baby a pacifier? \n</i></b></font></br>
	<br>\t• Pacifiers may cause the baby to skip a feeding or delay time between 
	feedings because the babies instinct to suck is being satisfied with an 
	artificial nipple \n</br>
	<br>\t• Your baby may have difficulty latching to your nipple properly after 
	having a pacifier because of the different shape and texture—this is called 
	nipple confusion \n</br>
	<br>\t• Nipple confusion may also lead to sore nipples and ineffective milk 
	transfer \n</br></p>
	
<p><br><font color='#EA8976'><b><i>When can I consider giving a pacifier to my baby?\n</i></b></font></br>
	<br>\t• Most experts recommend waiting at least 4 weeks to introduce a pacifier
	to allow your milk supply to establish itself and ensure your baby is 
	breastfeeding frequently enough \n</br>
	<br>\t• Even better would be to wait 6-8 weeks, so that your milk supply is 
	fully established and you aren’t losing any of the much needed nipple
	stimulation to the baby sucking on a pacifier instead of breastfeeding \n</br></p>
	</string>
</resources>
